# Sofia Costamagna

# FRONTEND DEVELOPER - UX/UI

#### CONTACT INFORMATION

sofiacostamagna45@gmail.com

**(**+54) 3874545109

Salta - Argentina

Open to relocate

EU passport

in <u>Linkedin</u>

GitHub

Portfolio

#### **EDUCATION**

• Full Stack Developer

Henry Bootcamp. 800 hours of theoretical and practical training. 2023.

Link: Certificate

#### COURSE

UX/UI Design

Codo a Codo - **In Progress**. 20 weeks, 198 hours.

• UX/UI Design and Figma

Udemy- Duration: 22 hours, 43 articles.

Advanced Excel

UBA (University of Buenos Aires), theoretical and practical training. 2020.

Payroll Processing

UBA (University of Buenos Aires), theoretical and practical training. 2022.

#### LANGUAGE

English Language

C1 - Advanced

Link: Certificate

• Fluent in Spanish.

## **VOLUNTEERS**

· Volunteer at Techo NGO

Active member of the training and volunteer team, where I contributed to the creation of fundraising campaigns, volunteer recruitment activities, and recreational events.

#### PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

I'm a Frontend developer specialized in technologies such as React, Redux, Bootstrap, CSS, Tailwind, Vue, Next.js and JavaScript. Additionally, I am studying and perfecting myself in UX/UI design, where creativity meets functionality. My experience in human resources has provided me with strong communication and people management skills. Furthermore, living in Canada for a few months broadened my horizon by exposing me to various cultures and languages, an experience that I deeply value.

I consider myself a responsible person committed to constantly expanding my knowledge and skills in this constantly evolving field. Valuing continuous learning and personal growth, I am always willing to acquire new skills.

### WORK EXPERIENCE

Frontend Developer and Junior UX/UI Designer

Ambassadoria, Aug 2023 - Nov 2023

A member of the Frontend and Junior UX/UI development team at Ambassadoria, contributing intuitive and appealing solutions. Specializing in user interface design, utilizes Figma, TypeScript, and Next.js to enhance the continuous development of the platform.

Front-End Developer

No Country, Sep 2023 - Sep 2023

As a member of the Frontend development team, used technologies such as React, Next.js, and React Hook Form to create exceptional user experiences. Collaborated on the design of the user interface in Figma.

LINK: **Mate Speak** 

VIDEO: Mate Speak-video

Front-End Developer

No Country, Aug 2023 - Sep 2023

A member of the Frontend development team, using JavaScript, React, and Vue. Collaborated with the UX/UI team in Figma and efficiently managed work on GitHub

LINK: MeSumo

VIDEO: MeSumo-video

Human Resources Administrator

Sanatorio Anchorena, Aug 2020-Sep2022

Led the management of nursing staff, overtime calculations, and personnel selection. Managed contracts, records, and coordinated the Covid Vaccination Plan. Provided administrative support to the Teaching department.

# **PROJECTS**

#### PetBook

Henry, May 2023 - May 2023

I contributed to a non-profit website dedicated to pet adoption. I used JavaScript, React, Redux, and Tailwind CSS for the Frontend development. It includes payment gateways through MercadoPago and Google authentication.

LINK: **Petbook** 

VIDEO: Petbook-video

# Videogames

Henry, April 2023 - April 2023

It's a Single Page Application using technologies like React, Redux, Node, Express, and Sequelize. I implemented basic styling and design resources to enhance the user experience (UX/UI).

• LINK: Videogames